[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word in this sentence is incorrectly used:  The new trivia mix was answered by Joe and me.", "correct_answer": "mix", "incorrect_answers": ["me", "answered", "trivia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The following words were spoken by the character Carl Denham in which 1933 movie: Oh, no.  It wasnt the airplanes. It was Beauty killed the Beast?", "correct_answer": "King Kong", "incorrect_answers": ["The Beast", "Beauty and the Beast", "The Bride of the Beast"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many legs does a spider have?", "correct_answer": "8", "incorrect_answers": ["6", "4", "10"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Major League, in the tiebreaker game for the playoffs against the NY Yankees, the Indians are down 2-0 before Cerrano hits a two-run homer to tie. In what inning did Cerrano hit his homer?", "correct_answer": "7th", "incorrect_answers": ["8th", "6th", "9th"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This directors movies usually have Gothic elements in them. He directed Ed Wood, Edward Scissorhands, Pee-Wees Big Adventure, and Beetlejuice.", "correct_answer": "Tim Burton", "incorrect_answers": ["Spike Jonze", "Michael  Gondry", "Gore Verbinski"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Lincoln delivered his Gettysburg Address he was not  the main speaker. Who was the main speaker?", "correct_answer": "Edward Everett", "incorrect_answers": ["General Grant", "Mrs. Lincoln", "General Meade"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the behavior of rabbits?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They are very easily startled.", "They run and hide immediately when they feel threatened.", "They are always alert."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country has a plain green flag?", "correct_answer": "Libya", "incorrect_answers": ["Lithuania", "Ireland", "Dominica"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the director of the 2001 science fiction movie Planet of the Apes?", "correct_answer": "Tim Burton", "incorrect_answers": ["James Cameron", "Steven Spielberg", "Martin Scorsese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "x^2+y^2=r^2 is which equation?", "correct_answer": "the equation of a circle", "incorrect_answers": ["the equation of a parabola", "the equation of a right triangle", "the equation of a hyperbola"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This soul singer recorded the song Dock of the Bay  in 1967,  three days prior to his death in a plane crash.", "correct_answer": "Otis Redding", "incorrect_answers": ["Bob Dylan", "Paul Banks", "Neil Sedaka"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the USA we often see commercials for Subway sandwiches. They usually feature a man who went  from 425 pounds to 190 pounds because of a diet  based on Subways menu. What is his name?", "correct_answer": "Jared Fogel", "incorrect_answers": ["Jared Leto", "Jared Nugent", "Jared Lamanite"]}]